Have you seen
our bank statement?
Can this be right?
I know.
God, I haven't seen my savings
take a hit like this
since I was a kid and they
came up with Doublestuf Oreos.
What happened to all
of our money?
Well, I'm not sure
exactly what they did,
but I'm inclined
to blame Enron.
Well, I guess with you
doing the internship,
we're just spending more
than we're bringing in.
Yeah, maybe I should quit
and get a job that pays.
But you're finally doing
something that you love.
I can't ask you
to give that up.
Although it would be nice
if the thing that you loved
is, you know, finding gold.
You know what,
you know what?
I think we're making
too big a deal out of this.
Okay, so we pay our bills
a little late this month,
and maybe next month
we cut back on a few things.
And maybe we start eating
out of Joey's refrigerator
for a change.
You're a chef.
What can you make out
of baking soda and beer?
All right, worst case scenario,
is we borrow some money
from my parents.
No. We're not borrowing money.
Why not?
Because we don't do that.
We are Bings.
If there's one thing
my father taught me
it was...
well, to always knock before
going into the pool house.
But the other thing was
never borrow money.
Wow, I had no idea
you had this much pride.
That's right, I do.
I am your man.
And I am going to get us
through this situation,
even if it means
you working twice as hard.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
I'm going to go.
Why?
I haven't been home
in a couple days
and I need to get
some more clothes.
You don't have to go.
I have something
that will fit you.
I put that tube top on
as a joke.
I want you to stay.
I want to stay too,
but I've gotten about
as much use out
of these boxers
as I can.
Why don't you turn them
inside...?
Done it.
I'll be back
in a couple of hours.
I'll miss you.
Me, too.
You know what?
I just realized something.
I don't want to go home.
Great. Okay, I'll go get
the tube top.
No, no.
What I mean is,
I hate going back
to my apartment now.
Partly because I live above
a known crack den, but...
you know,
mostly because
when I'm there,
I really miss you.
So...
do you want to move in together?
Wow, Mike Hanigan.
You sure know how to make
a girl say, "Hell, yeah."
So we're doing it?
Yeah, let's do it.
Let's live together.
Wow, we're really going
to move in together.
Yeah.
I've always wanted
to live with a guy.
"You pick up your socks."
"Put down the toilet seat."
"No, we are not having
sex anymore!"
It's going to be fun.
Hey, Joey.
Hey.
Listen, I need
to know that...
that what I'm
about to ask you,
will never get
back to Chandler.
I'd be lying if I said
I hadn't thought
about it myself.
But Chandler is
my best friend.
It would be wrong.
Good, but wrong.
Okay, first of all,
it would be great.
But that's not what
I'm here to talk
to you about.
I need to borrow
some money.
Oh, I don't know, Monica.
You know
lending friends money
is always a mistake.
But Chandler lent you money.
And I think he would tell you
it was a mistake.
Come on, I need it
for some rent
and some other bills.
Oh, uh... how much?
$2,000.
$2,000?!
What do you think I am,
a soap opera star?
Yeah.
That's right, I am.
Hi, you guys.
Hey.
What's in the bag?
Oh, well, you know
how Emma
started crawling?
I realized that this place
is very unsafe for a baby.
So I went to the store
and I got some stuff
to baby-proof the apartment.
Oh, God.
Baby-proofing.
Why is this such
a big deal now?
You know, when
I was a kid,
it was like, "Oops, Joey
fell down the stairs."
Or, "Oops,
Joey electrocuted
himself again."
Anyway, um...
Are you going
to get a handyman
to install this stuff?
No, I was just going
do it myself.
( chuckles )
You're going to do it?
Yeah. Why?
You don't think
a woman can do this?
Oh, women can.
You... can't.
Monica, will you
please tell Joey
that he is a pig.
You're a pig.
And you
can't do this.
Wha...?!
What? Come on, I found
the hardware store
all by myself.
The hardware store's
right down the street.
There is a hardware store
right down the street?
Okay, you guys...
Okay, we've
got great news.
Phoebe and I are
moving in together.
Congratulations!
That's great.
That's great news.
I know.
It's so exciting.
You know, I've never
lived with a guy before.
It's just like living
with a girl,
only they don't steal
your makeup.
Unless they're playing
"this-is-what-my-sister-
would-look-like.
Yeah, she's
not so cute.
I'm going to go
to the bathroom.
Okay, well, you put down
the toilet seat.
Yes, dear.
Is that a bit
you guys do?
Uh-huh.
We're playing you two.
We don't do that.
Tell her
we don't do that.
Yes, dear.
I can't believe you guys
are moving in together.
I'm happy for you guys.
I hear wedding bells.
Monica, slow down, okay?
I'm just excited
to be living with him.
You know, I mean,
I don't know--
can I see someday
being married to Mike?
Sure. Yeah.
You know, I could picture myself
walking down the aisle
in a wedding dress that
highlights my breasts
in an obvious yet classy way.
You know,
but do I want
that house in Connecticut?
You know, near the good schools
where Mike and I could send
little Sophie and Mike, Jr.?
Oh, my God, I do.
Phoebe, I had no idea
you were so conventional.
I know. I guess I am.
Oh, my God, load up the Volvo.
I want to be a soccer mom.
You ready to go?
Yeah, you bet,
roomie.
Don't you mean "groomie"?
What are you
talking about?
Please. These guys.
We haven't even
moved in yet
and they have us
picking out
china patterns.
( nervous laugh )
I know.
We should go.
China patterns!
This is easy.
Can't do this.
Wow, seriously, can't do this.
CHANDLER:
Hey, Joe.
Listen, um... I need
to ask you a favor
and we can't tell Monica
anything about it.
I thought you didn't have
secrets from Monica.
And that will remain
the official party line.
Look, Monica and I are having
a little financial trouble.
Yeah, I know.
What? What do you mean you know?
Uh...
I just figured it out,
you know.
I mean, you're not working
and the economy is bad.
Oh, right.
( quietly ):
That is the fastest
I have ever thought.
Anyway, uh...
I need to borrow some money.
Oh, sure. How much?
$2,000?
Yes. $2,000 exactly.
How did you know that?
Uh, well, I, uh... I know
how much you used to make
and I know how much
your rent is.
Oh, okay.
I am on fire.
Listen, this is
really nice.
Di... did you write a check
to Monica for $2,000?
Did Monica borrow
money from you?
Uh... kind of.
I can't believe her.
Did she tell you we were
having money problems?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
It wasn't... it wasn't
because of your money problems.
It was for something for her.
What?
Something personal.
What would she get
for herself for $2,000
that she wouldn't
tell me about?
Excuse me.
Boob job.
I don't want her
to get a boob job.
That's crazy.
It's not that crazy, okay?
Making them smaller--
that would be crazy.
Oh, hey, I wanted
to ask you
about Monica's little
"groomie" joke.
Oh, all right.
Well, I think the reason
people laughed
is it's a play
on the word "roomie."
No. I get the joke.
Sophisticated as it was.
No, the thing
I want to say is...
Maybe we should have talked
about this before.
Us living together--
you're not expecting
a proposal, right?
Oh, no, no,
not at all.
Okay.
We're just moving in
right now.
We'll see where it goes.
Yeah, well, that's the thing.
For me, it's as far
as it can ever go.
What do you mean?
Look, Phoebe, I...
I love you very much.
But I never want
to get married again.
Oh.
Wow.
It's just, my first
marriage was...
you know, such
a disaster
that I kind of lost faith
in the whole idea.
Was it really
that bad?
At one point near the end,
she deliberately defecated on...
Okay, well, that's bad, yeah.
But don't you think
it might be different
with someone else?
Perhaps a blonde
who always uses a toilet.
Except for once
in the ocean.
Look, it's not about
who I would marry.
I was certain the first
time I got married
it would last forever,
and I was totally wrong.
But it just...
Look, Phoebe,
it's not about you.
I just never want
to get married again.
Huh.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay with that?
Because if not, maybe
us moving in together
isn't the best idea.
No. Oh, I definitely
don't want to get married.
No, I just wanted
to make sure
you didn't want to, too.
Whew.
Okay.
'Cause, you know,
if we move in
and you start
changing your mind,
there's going to be
hell to pay, mister.
Trust me, I will never...
Yeah, I get that, yeah.
Hey.
Hi.
So, you gave in
and decided to call someone?
Yeah. I don't know
who I was kidding.
I can barely use chopsticks.
You're all set.
Oh, thank you so much.
Oh, oh, wait.
You forgot your, um...
your game.
Thank you.
Hey, Rach.
There she is,
my perfectly proportioned wife.
Don't look at me.
I never get his jokes.
Thank you.
No, no, don't thank
me, thank you.
Do you know
there is not one thing
that I would change about you?
Not one single thing.
And definitely not...
two single things.
Okay, you're being weird.
Do you want sex
or did you do something bad?
No, no, no.
I just love the way you look.
I am warm for your form.
Okay, um, you know the old
classics, like, you know,
"you look nice"?
They're still okay.
Well, yes, yes,
but "you look nice"
can mean that I'm saying,
like, your face looks nice.
I want to compliment your body.
I mean,
I wouldn't change it at all.
And more specifically,
I wouldn't want anything
to get any bigger.
Okay.
I mean, you wouldn't want
any part of me
to get any bigger, would you?
Don't answer that.
Just when you thought that dude
couldn't get any weirder.
I know.
I know, why do you think
he was so worried about me
getting bigger?
I don't know.
I mean, what brought that on?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, you know,
we're trying to get pregnant,
so he's probably starting
to freak out about the fact
that my body's going to change.
No, you really think
that's what it is?
You heard him?
"No bigger, you're perfect.
Just don't get any bigger."
My God, he sounded just like
my high school wrestling coach.
You know what?
I'm going to have
to talk to Chandler.
Yeah. If you
don't, I will.
Of course your body's
going to change.
Your breasts are
going to get bigger.
Your ass is going
to get bigger.
You're going to lose
bladder control.
God, it's just such
a magical time.
( knocking )
Hi.
Hey.
Listen, I wanted to ask you
something about marriage.
Oh, great, now you're
seeking me out to make jokes?
I mean, I can see
if we're all hanging out,
but to come to my home.
No.
No, I really want to know
how you feel about it.
Why?
Mike doesn't ever want
to get married.
Never?
Never.
Wow.
Well, are you still going
to move in with him?
Well, I want to, but...
I just wanted you to tell me
that marriage really isn't
that big a deal, you know?
That I won't be missing out
on anything.
That marriage stinks.
Yeah... marriage stinks.
I mean
if you want to see a man
gain weight
and a woman stop shaving,
get them married.
That's not how you really feel,
is it?
No, I'm sorry.
Look, I know it's
not what you want
to hear right now,
but I can't help it--
I love marriage.
Seriously, you divorce-o?
If you have to call me a name,
I prefer Ross, the Divorcer.
It's just cooler.
Look, look...
I know my marriages didn't
exactly work out, but...
you know, I loved
being that committed
to another person.
And Carol and I had
some good times
before she became
a lesbian...
and once afterward.
Anyway, I-I'm sorry.
Oh, that's okay.
That's how you feel.
But, come on, I mean,
living together will be great.
I mean, you guys have
so much fun, and you love Mike.
I do love Mike.
Yeah, see?
And you were so excited
about moving in together before,
and you know what,
you should be; it's a big deal.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Yeah, thanks.
This helped. Thanks.
The Divorcer to the rescue.
It's not cooler.
Yeah, I just heard it.
( chuckling excitedly )
Rach?
Rachel!
So, I can't do anything I like?!
Hey, Rach.
Aah... perfection.
Wouldn't change a thing,
not a thing.
Yeah, honey?
Yeah?
About that.
Um... I'm going to change.
Yes, but, honey, you...
you don't have to.
I'm going to get bigger.
Honey, I...
I love your breasts
the way they are.
Uh, fascist.
Well, my breasts are going
to get bigger
whether you like it or not.
And you know what?
It's not just my breasts.
My ass is going
to get bigger, too.
Your ass?
Yeah, and don't be surprised
if her hands and her feet
get bigger, too.
They do that?
It's kind of a package deal.
God, why... why would you want
to do that to yourself?
I thought it was something
that we both wanted.
( sighs )
All right, look, if it
means that much to you,
I may be able to get on
board with the big boobs,
but the giant ass and
the big clown feet?
Oh, my God,
Chandler.
If you can't handle this,
what are you going to be like
in the hospital
with the blood
and the screaming
and the little person
that's shooting out of her?
What?
Joey, why did you tell Chandler
that Monica was getting
a boob job?
Because she is.
Joey, Chandler knows
I borrowed the money.
Mm-hmm, for your boob job.
Joe.
Stop it.
It's over.
Okay, so, I'm out $4,000
and nobody's boobs
are getting any bigger?
Hey, hey, what do you guys
think about this:
Ross, the Divorce Force.
Better.
Yeah?
Very cool.
Hey, Pheebs, you know,
I-I'm really glad you came
to talk to me the other day
and I hope I was
a little helpful.
Oh, yeah, you were helpful.
Yeah. No, thank you.
Good, good.
Yeah, 'cause the more
I thought about it,
the more I realized
I don't think marriage
is necessarily
the right path for you.
What do you mean?
Well, I know the other day
in the coffeehouse
you were all caught up
in the whole soccer-mom thing,
but... is that really you?
I mean, can you honestly
picture yourself in a Volvo?
They are awfully boxy.
I mean,
I don't know,
you'd be so bored with marriage.
I mean, it's so... normal.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Hey, hey, can I help?
CHANDLER:
Well, we climbed up
four flights of stairs,
maneuvered a narrow hallway,
dodged a rabid pit bull,
but these last feet
are where it gets really tricky.
You know, sometimes
your words-- they hurt.
Hey, uh, where do
you guys want this?
Yeah, seriously, 'cause
this is really heavy.
I mean, not for me,
because I'm only
pretending to hold it,
but for these guys.
Just one last time,
um, the marriage thing,
there's no wiggle room?
None at all?
No, but you don't want
to get married either, right?
Right.
Except that I do
want to get married.
Couldn't have had
this conversation
down at the truck, huh?
What? You want to get married?
Someday.
And... hernia.
I haven't exactly
had a normal life
and I never really felt
like I was missing out
on anything,
but... it just,
it feels like
now it's my turn
to have some of
the regular stuff.
If you wanted
to get married,
why didn't you say
something before?
Because I just didn't know
how much I wanted it,
and I-I love you
and I wanted to live with you.
I want to live with you, too.
I mean, let's do that.
But I-I don't think I can.
It was-it was okay to move in
when I didn't know
what was going to happen,
but I-I can't move in
knowing nothing is ever
going to happen.
Can you at least try
living together?
I mean, you might change
your mind about marriage.
Are you going to change yours?
No.
Me neither.
Um... I think I need
to be with someone
who wants what I want.
But I don't want this to end.
Well, I don't want it
to end, either.
I can't believe
this is going to end.
I guess I'll have
my stuff picked up.
Yeah, okay.
Okay, so, uh...
Good-bye.
Take it easy, Mike.
Good luck.
Bye, Mike.
See you
later, Mike.
Bye-bye, now.
I'm so sorry,
Pheebs.
We're all sorry.
Look on the bright side,
I mean, at least you won't have
to live with this ugly chair.
That was here already, huh?
I love you.
( kissing )
Aah! I did it!
I did it! Ha-ha!
All right.
I better take all I can carry.
Who knows when I'll be able
to get in here again, huh?
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org